One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Oh! Master!
Ruins of Laboratory #1 and #2
I got all this stuff sticking outta me!
It's a furball!
That's Guard Point!
Just by visualizing them,
you can freely transform between six different forms.
This body ain't very stable!
It takes practice!
Hey! Don't play on me!
What did you say?! The samurai left?!
Yes.
Dammit! I thought that it's been too quiet!
Just a short while ago, I told him about a fellow I met who's nothing but a torso.
He wanted to know where I had met him...
and I told him that we parted ways near the lake.
Then he ran out of here.
I was distracted by Nami-san's glorious body
so I let my guard down!
Even though it's inconvenient for you?
The one who took him outside
when he was just a head who couldn't move...
was me.
It might have been uncalled for, but it was what I had to do.
If he gets killed now, it'll be my fault.
I see.
Even though he's a samurai, he doesn't have a torso to hold a sword so all he can do is run away from battle.
Well then, shall we go and do what we must?
That goddamn asshole.
Luffy! I'm gonna head out for a bit, okay?
Yeah, sure.
Okay, I'll show you the way...
so may I see your panties?
For sure!
Oh, right! We need a camera for an opportunity like this!
Stop right there!
Zoro, you're going too.
Huh?
If Zoro is there,
Sanji-kun will be in fight-mode at all times!
Why do I need to search for that farting samurai just because you're an idiot?! You pervert!
No one wants you here, anyway!
I can't believe I'm stuck with a dumbass
who I can't even share this happiness with!
I was mercilessly struck.
Do you think my bones were broken?
No, all that's broken is my dream to see those panties.
Idiot!
Pervert!
So, what should we do about your bodies?
The most important thing to do now
is get our bodies back.
I don't want to be this pervert for another millisecond!
Are you trying to kill me with praise?
Please don't make that face with Chopper's body.
Ever.
The real problem is those damn kids. They're a real pain in the ass.
Franky, I'd appreciate it
if you didn't speak with that face.
Ever.
No!
That's not what I want!
Raccoon Dog-chan, how does it look?
We'll know in a moment.
Huh! That means...
What happened? Sind? Are you hurt?
Are you okay?
What happened?!
It hurts...
Chopper. He says it hurts.
Cure him.
Mocha!
What's happening to all of you?
Doran, too?
All the big kids are collapsing!
What happened?
Chopper, what is it? Are the kids really sick?
No.
Sind, is there anything that you want right now?
What do you usually do at times like this?
Usually?
After the examination... then...
Then what?
Then they give us candy.
Candy?
It's delicious.
Everyone loves the candy.
It's really great.
It's all fizzy and smoke comes out.
That's right... We eat it...
And when you eat it...
you get this happy feeling.
It might make me feel better.
Brownbeard, was it?
What do you know about this?
These kids aren't sick!
What are you talking about? I patrol outside,
so I don't know what goes on in the laboratory...
but those kids have a serious disease!
Hang in there, kids.
Hey, Chopper.
Even the little ones look like they're starting to hurt.
The ever-compassionate Master
went out of his way to gather those kids,
and he's been donating his medical knowledge
to treat them.
He's a tenderhearted scientist!
It hurts...
Ally?
Look, there's your proof!
After missing a single day of treatment,
those kids have already started to collapse from pain.
No!
Chopper, what have you learned?
NHC-10. That's what I found in the kids' bodies.
There were only faint traces, but it's...
a narcotic!
A narcotic?!
Throughout the world, only a few scientists in select countries are allowed to have it.
I know about it because Doctorine used it.
There are some legitimate uses for the drug,
but only in the smallest amounts.
It's extremely addictive if you take too much.
The children have been taking the drug every day for a long time now.
They've become chronically addicted to it.
Their bodies crave the next dose in order to stop the pain.
Why?! Why would they have this in their system?!
It's so that they can't run away from the lab, isn't it?!
What is this "god of salvation" of yours really doing to these kids?!
If you speak ill of Master, you'll pay for it!
Chopper, what do we do?
They're all collapsing, one after another!
Candy! Candy!
You need candy?
Should I go get some from the building?
No!
They must never eat the candy again!
They've been using it to give the drug to the children
without them knowing it!
Strawhat man.
You'll bring me the candy?
I can't. If Chopper says you can't have it,
then you can't have it.
He's our doctor. Trust him!
Why?
Why? Why?
Sind, what happened?
I'm scared.
You said that you'd bring me some!
Didn't you!? Didn't you say that you'd bring me some!
What strength!
Stop it, Sind!
I've never seen Sind like this before.
What strength!
Giants are pretty strong, I guess their children are too.
This strong?
Why won't you give me the candy?!
Sind's not a giant!
We were all normal size when we came to this island.
I thought the disease was making us get bigger.
Nothing else is wrong with us.
There's no disease
that makes normal humans grow into giants.
Giants are always giant.
The longer a kid has been here, the bigger they become.
That means...
their pituitary glands have started producing an abnormal amount of growth hormone.
Candy!
These kids...
are being experimented on!
Candy!
Hold yourself together, Ally!
I want candy!
What was this "Master" thinking,
using narcotics on such young kids?!
Candy!
The other kids are starting to go wild!
Candy! Candy! Candy!
There's nothing we can do.
Nami!
Sind! Quit it!
Should I fight 'em?
No! Outta the way, Luffy!
Usopp! Don't hurt them!
Idiot! Of course I know that!
I knew that they must have been kidnapped.
Let us out of here!
I wanna see Mommy and Daddy!
Luffy.
It's tragic. They don't even know that they've been manipulated.
They want to go home!
They want to be with their parents!
We have to help them!
Luffy, I want to save them too.
Well then, I guess we'll take 'em all home.
Stupid, it's not that easy.
There's a mountain of problems!
That's right. Besides, this is all just our interpretation.
Unless we ask the ringleader directly, we won't know any of this for sure.
Isn't it that Master guy?
But Zoro, Sanji, and Brook
went to go look for that samurai.
Uh... Well, whatever.
Right! Let's go back to the laboratory...
to find Master.
I should stay here.
I can never forgive Master...
and I want to kick his ass...
but I'm worried about the children.
I have to look after them.
Ye-Yeah! That's right! I'll also have to stay!
Hey Nami! That's a dirty trick! You're just scared!
But it'll be pretty bad if the kids get violent again.
We'll tie the big ones up like this.
I don't like it, but...
There's no helping it.
They're heavyweights when they get violent.
And we don't know when they'll wake up.
So, who's going to go where?
The four of us have to get together and meet Trafalgar,
or we won't get our bodies back.
But it's fine the way it is!
This is definitely not fine! Take it seriously!
The heart of Smoker, Vice Admiral of Navy Unit G-5.
What a thoughtful present, Law.
There's no doubt who won that battle.
They'll want to report what happened, and since
they lost their ship they'll come to take one of ours.
Of course, I've already made arrangements.
What about Straw-Hatter?
He's not a problem either.
His crew is being dealt with,
and the children will be brought back.
Well, the kids will eventually want to come back
even if they're left alone.
Monet says that we should take appropriate caution when dealing with the Straw Hat Pirates.
That's why I chose to send the duo after them.
The two who never miss their mark.
The hit men of the mountain.
The Yeti Cool Brothers.
Only six left.
I thought they'd give us more trouble...
but it's probably best if we finish it quickly.
Just like these three...
Coolly.
It's me. Right off the top,
we took care of three of them.
Pirate Hunter Zoro.
The Cat Burglar.
The Soul King.
You'll find the corpses
at the bottom of a cliff in zone F-16.
We'll leave the disposal to you.
You killed them?
Isn't that why we're here?
Well... I guess it's...
If you don't want people to die, then don't call us!
S-Sorry! Master said either way was...
Hey, hey. Don't get hot under the collar.
Woops, I slipped.
Let's go, coolly.
Please continue with the contract.
Caesar Clown's Laboratory
Did you hear that? They're already dead, Monet.
I see.
How unexpected.
The Straw Hat Pirates are members of
the Worst Generation, the same as Law.
The government is keeping just as close an eye
on them as they are on Blackbeard.
The newspapers made grand claims
that they had completely recovered,
so I thought they'd be more impressive.
Don't you agree, Law?
You know them, don't you?
Two years ago at Sabaody, and again at Marineford...
You've gotten involved with Straw Hat twice.
What?
Does this mean that you called them here?
Didn't I already tell you this?
Until we crossed paths at the entrance,
I had no idea that you'd locked them in the laboratory.
If I had known, I would have warned you.
Don't let your guard down
just because you've locked them in a room.
Because of your naivety,
I wasn't able to bluff the Navy into going away.
I don't want what's going on here to leak out
any more than you do.
Master!
I'm doing an experiment. Call later.
But a Warlord's here!
What?
You're going to stay on Punk Hazard?
It took a lot of effort for me to get to this island
since it can't be reached with a Log.
I did it because there was
a hidden Government facility here.
What's your objective?
Since Dr. Vegapunk formerly used this lab,
there should still be evidence
of what the World Government is up to.
That is to say, projects that they're working on today
should have started here.
Anyway, as long as I'm free to walk around
the island and laboratory, that'll be sufficient.
I can help you out around here, as well.
Neither of us has to get involved in the other's business. Of course, don't tell anyone that I'm here.
Not even Joker.
You seem very well informed! How do you know about him?
Would you prefer it if I was an ignorant fool that didn't know what he was doing?
Well now, aren't we two birds of a feather?
We can't trust each other,
but your proposition seems harmless.
Right, Monet?
From North Blue, the Surgeon of Death.
You have the Ope Ope Fruit ability. I see that you're a doctor.
On this island, there are many ex-convicts
who lost the use of their legs to the poison gas.
Can you help them?
Well, if you'd actually called for help,
I imagine you'd have been more clever about it.
You went through all of the effort of ingratiating yourself to the Government and becoming a Warlord,
so I suppose you wouldn't try to expose this island.
Sorry.
A moment ago...
you said that if you left the kids from
the Biscuits Room alone, they'd come back.
What did you mean by that?
Every day I give them a drug-laced candy.
It's sweet and fizzy to the taste...
and releases an intoxicating gas into the mouth.
They're all addicted to it.
I can't have them going back home, after all.
You're twisted, alright.
Reminds me of a certain someone.
Aren't you going to join the battle with the Navy?
If you need me, call me.
I'll cut the head off of anyone you need.
It's hard to handle people who are so sharp.
There it is again! What is going on?!
This isn't an earthquake.
Are we under attack? It's an enemy!
Was that an explosion?
It's in the direction we came from.
Could it have something to do
with whoever made this footprint?
There's something out there, alright.
They feel like monsters. Two of 'em!
Let's go back! Nami and Chopper are in trouble!
Y-Yeah!
Oh no! If this place collapses, the children will...
Luffy! Come back here!
They'll never make it in time!
The two of us have to deal with this!
Can you see them, Chopper?
How many enemies are there? What are they like?
There's...
nobody out here at all!
There's no way.
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Oh, I fell asleep.
It's getting noisy out there.
Is somebody here to save me?
Law? Master?
No, this is the snow mountain...
so it's got to be them!
Hey, Brownie! You know something.
Who's coming?
You'd better answer, or else I'll do this!
Beam!
Beam! Beam! Beam! Beam!
You're disrespecting the beam!
Searching for them is pointless. They never show themselves.
Even we don't know what their faces look like.
But once you hire them
and give them their money, they always get the kill.
All we know about them is that their feet are huge,
but their voices are quiet.
Oh, and another thing we know is that
they are giant beast-men covered in fur!
They're the hit man duo
who appear in blizzards on the mountain.
Oh yeah, we also know their names, Rock and Scotch.
People call them...
the Yeti Cool Brothers!
They were born in an undisclosed snowy country,
and their ages are-
You know loads of stuff about them!
But nobody knows what they look like.
They're both gigantic and powerful!
They've come to save me.
You're already on their hit list.
Brownbeard?
You're on the hit list as well.
What's with this guy?!
He's huge, but I didn't hear him at all!
Wha?! Are you Rock?
I'm Scotch.
I thought you said something ridiculous.
I must have misheard you.
I nearly had a heart attack.
Master must have contracted you to save me?
So hurry up and free me from these chains,
then kill the Straw Hat-
You didn't mishear me. Master put a hit on you.
There's no way!
Listen to this.
Oh, and that guy... What was his name again?
That voice!
He went and got himself captured.
That stupid hairy-faced man...
He was famous for being an idiot.
Ohhh right, Brownbeard.
Eh, Master?!
That's him?
He's an idiot so he's easy to use,
but he has become a burden.
We don't need him anymore.
Kill him.
Hey, look! There's smoke!
Nami! Chopper! Are you okay?!
You're Brownbeard, aren't you?
You did well to make it this far.
You're all better now. You can relax.
Good work.
Master! Today was quiet, as normal!
I see. Brownbeard, you are a most reliable guard.
Oh, not at all.
I don't believe it.
I don't believe it!
Master!
Don't be so hot-headed. Die coolly.
Hey Scotch.
There's another one!
Quit shooting.
You'll bring this place down and kill the kids.
Oh. That wouldn't be cool.
Brownbeard!
How terrible! Their own ally!
Look there, the captain has come back.
Taking them out comes first.
What's that? They're huge!
Giants?
No, they look a little bit different.
You better not have hurt my crew!
Wha... He's gone!
Luffy!
Are you okay?!
Sorry! They got Nami!
This is the only one
that we're supposed to capture alive.
A robot with Vegapunk's laser, huh?
Now we can kill everyone else.
Okay. Let's enjoy the hunt as much as possible.
Coolly.
Laboratory - Backdoor
Huh?
Law-san, where are you headed?
We just ran into the Navy not too far from here!
I don't care.
Where I go... is my business.